{
    "subject": "resource/Steely_Dan",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Steely Dan is from the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8597629070281982,
            "question": "Where is Steely Dan from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8259916305541992,
            "question": "In which nation did Steely Dan originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8023332357406616,
            "question": "From which country did Steely Dan emerge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7984788417816162,
            "question": "Is Steely Dan an American band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6838671565055847,
            "question": "Where is Steely Dan based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6611780524253845,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Steely Dan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.649362325668335,
            "question": "What country are Steely Dan associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.638085126876831,
            "question": "Steely Dan's origin is in what part of the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6216509938240051,
            "question": "To what nation does Steely Dan belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3958773612976074,
            "question": "Steely Dan's musical roots lie in which country?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Steely Dan is from the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8876_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To what nation does Steely Dan belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8876_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Steely Dan's origin is in what part of the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8876_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country are Steely Dan associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8876_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8876_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8876_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8876_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8876_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8876_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8876_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8876_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8876_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8876_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8876_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Steely Dan was founded in New York, which is part of the United States. Given this information, it can be inferred that Steely Dan is indeed from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}